Aseani Miller's FullStack Resume

Cell: (510) 355 5688 Email: milleraseani@gmail.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/aseani-miller-17b40918b GitHub: https://github.com/seandmiller

Portfolio: https://github.com/seandmiller/My-Portfolio

Profile

I'm a Full Stack developer who has programmed in both Python and Javascript, I can traverse the dom and create automated tasks such as sending an email in an interval.

Relevant Skills

Experience with Javascript programming

February - 2020

Written React code and understand the component model

Created a mock search engine with a simulated api get request that recommends results based

on what you've typed in the search engine

React Component Based Architecture has really taught me a lot about the importance of damage control in your code, with this model one bug in your code just affects one component and not the entire program.

Experience with traversing the dom

Created automation in gmail by going through the dom and selecting the elements in the correct sequence. The result was being able to send a gmail message all in one go, which I then was able to put into a loop.

Python Programming with various projects on github

August-2020

Experience with Linux operating system

Creating files, making directories, installing and updating software via terminal on linux chrome os

i've learned alot from using this version of linux, the problems are very rare and hard to find easy solutions, the experience from using it has helped with solving technical problems

Experience with FastAPI and creating api's

Creating an API endpoint and connecting it to a sqlite database

Understanding how to return JSON data in a format that's parseable to front end developers

Tkinter GUI experience

Rendering Graphical User Interface with data that I coded in the backend

Created a Connect Four game with this framework and added an Algorithm that determined who the winner is

MySQL

I know how to traverse the database as well as create them with MySQL workbench

• Soft Skills:

Experience with investing and the financial markets, CAGR of 60% starting from 2018 (as of 2020),

I used the above knowledge to create my own small pocket library, which I update as I improve on my programming skills

Github: https://github.com/seandmiller/inves_tools

Very Technical not just with programming but with the world overall

This is what led me to one of my first investments which was Tesla, I understand the economic output of their technology which led me to invest in them

Projects

• Image Translator: An Application purely built with python that downloads an image online or select one on your local machine parses the text off the image and then translates it into a desired language. Technologies used for this project are Tkinter, Pytesseract, Google trans, Requests and Opency.

Github: https://github.com/seandmiller/ImageTranslator

- Mock Ecommerce Search Engine: One of my first ever Reactjs projects. In this projects specifically I manipulated state, used the filter function and since filter returns a sequence data structure I used the map function over it and passed all the items into a Component named Search (better description is on the github)

 Github: https://github.com/seandmiller/EnterReactjs

 Letters General Assessment and brite with mothers The shire the efficiency is a fall to be a project the season of the same and the enterty of the enter
- Lottery Game: A game purely built with python. The object is of this game is to bankrupt the opponent through a series of bets. In this project I learned how to create animations and sounds on a GUI. Technologies used for this project are Tkinter, random and pygame.

 Github: https://github.com/seandmiller/lotto

Work Experience

Tesla Production Associate

October 2020 - June 2021

- -Working on the factory floor logging defects found on the vehicle
- -Maintaining the best quality for the vehicles by actively check for dirt and marks that can be scrubbed out thoroughly
- -Cleaning the vehicle before we paint it as to avoid as much defects as possible
- Transdev Self Autonomous Operator

June 2021 - August 2021

- -Responsible for logging odd behavior of the vehicle if incorrect
- -Checking to make sure the vehicle is fully functional before it begins its route
- -Looking through the software to see what the computer sees and to make sure its accurate

Education

• Bottega University online coding bootcamp

January- 2020 - current

• Google IT course - Technical Fundamentals

July 29th 2020 - Completed

Hobbies

Learning

Without this one particular hobby I wouldn't even be here, my curiosity spanned from the financial markets all the way to the technical side of most of the business's i've invested in

• Swimming

Swimming is one of my favorite things to do as your actively working out all parts of your body

Watching anime

I tend to watch anime when I need a mental breather for a technical problem or just to get away.